blockbuster.ca 2001-06-14

# BLOCKBUSTER VIDEO, Canada's Family Entertainment Store

Blockbuster Canada Co. (Blockbuster Canada) is committed to protecting our users' on-lineprivacy. To that end, we offer this statement to inform our users of how we define, gather and utilize personally identifiable information. Blockbuster Canada will take reasonable steps to protect member privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this policy and applicable law. 

Blockbuster Canada defines personally identifiable information as information about an identifiable individual that includes any combination of the following: a person's full name, address, telephone number, date of birth and/or email address. 

Blockbuster Canada can gather information about our users in two different ways:

  1. You supply it in response to a request from us, or
  2. Cookie Technology. 

Blockbuster Canada collects personally identifiable information from users when voluntarily submitted by a user, such as participating in a sweepstakes or contest, or subscription offers. We request that a user be 18 years of age or older before submitting personally identifiable information and we ask minors to get permission from their parents or legal guardian before submitting personally identifiable information. 

Blockbuster Canada utilizes cookie technology to process and identify order data. A cookie is a piece of information that is transferred to a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. If users so choose, they have the option to set their browser to refuse cookies. 

Blockbuster Canada may use personally identifiable information collected online to develop and improve the products, benefits and services we or select business partners offer to our members or web site users. Blockbuster Canada may also use email addresses or other personally identifiable information to contact users who directly communicate with Blockbuster Canada. For example, Blockbuster Canada may contact users to notify them that they have won a contest or sweepstakes or to provide a requested email newsletter. 

If you wish to opt-out of opportunities to receive promotional materials, products, or other communications from Blockbuster Canada, its affiliates, or their business partners, please write to: Privacy Relationship Manager, Blockbuster Canada Co. 191 The West Mall, Suite 800, Toronto, ON M9C 5K8. With the exception of users exercising the opt-out opportunity, Blockbuster Canada may, on occasion, disclose to their business partners certain personally identifiable information for use in marketing goods and services directly to blockbuster.ca users and BLOCKBUSTER members.

Blockbuster Canada may share and use user and member information in the ordinary course of its businesses, including account maintenance and debt collection.

Blockbuster Canada supports the requirements and intent of the Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information, CAN/CSA-Q 830-96 and will require employee and business partner compliance with the Model Code. 

Blockbuster Canada reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy from time to time.

Contact Us  
BLOCKBUSTER name, design and related marks are trademarks of Blockbuster Inc.  
© 2001 Blockbuster Inc. All Rights Reserved.
